hey everyone welcome back to our Channel
I am back with another interesting topic
in the Tosca automation playlist
now we have already seen how we can
execute our test cases manually by going
through each step and verifying it
manually on the system under test but
there is also a way through which you
can directly set your automation result
to either pass field or no result for
the specific execution entry
so let's see how you can do this
so if you go ahead and open a particular
execution list and then you go to the
execution entry
here uh currently it is set to pass but
if I want I can set this manually to
either past field or no result so when
you right click on the execution entry
you see a option called set result
now there are three options as I said
that is passed there is failed and no
result so I can set this to no result
and then it will ask me for a comment so
I can say manually set to no result
and then I can click on OK
and you will see that the recent
execution will be set to no result
also in the log info you will see who
has set this particular result so it was
set by admin
and it will also show you the specific
comment so manually set to no result
okay
similarly I can go ahead and again set
this result to field
and then I am going to see manually set
to field
okay and again you will see uh this test
case will now be filled in the login
flow also it will be highlighted that
this whole test case has failed it will
enter it into the start time into the
logs and also it will specify which user
has done that and why he has done that
in the comments
so it's a pretty uh easy and quick way
of manually setting a particular result
for your test cases in execution lists
this could be useful uh during releases
when you want to start freshly for a
particular test case you want to set it
to no result or maybe you have tested
that particular feature in your
application and you found it is not
working so you manually set this test
case to field
so this way you can modify the result of
any particular execution entry in your
execution lists
that's all for this particular video if
you have any questions then please leave
it in the comments if you like this
video then please subscribe to our
Channel
thanks for watching and I will see you
in the next video